So this is the logo for the brand Etro.
Big fan.
They usually have a lot of prints and paisleys and colors.
And you know, I love all them bangs.
But the bitery that I have witnessed.
This right here is an Etro skirt.
And I was like, that looks real familiar.
Because this right here is pretty much the same damn skirt,
except it's by South African designer Laduma for his line Maxosa.
And if I'm really trying to, like, really be on my South African designer,
I think it's like Maxosa.
But kids don't try this at all.
Here's the skirt in another color.
Yeah.
That looks a lot like the Etro skirt.
And you know what?
This came first.
So I just want to quickly refresh your memory that this is the Etro skirt.
This is me wearing an older version of the Maxosa skirt.
Do you see it?
Look.
Come on.
And this is the designer Laduma.
Now, who you think more authentically designs that skirt?
Him or some Italians?
Here's the thing.
Fashion is commerce, but first, it's art.
And what artists do is we create, we hone, and we perfect our style.
And when you take someone else's style, you are breaking the code of artist's ethics.
Now head over to Maxosa and get you some authentic Maxosa threads.
And do not buy that Etro stuff that looks like theirs.
Because they bite it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.